₹350 Bank understanding stocks are kept everywhere
Good morning Morning Ashish will start with the numbers
such long and yesterday we
saw that there was a lot of action by day
in the market and here if
you see then the profit that came is a
little better than expected, although the combine rates are still on the
higher side and there was an increase in the net on premium
but it is not meeting the expectations as well as the
claim rates because some claims in the motor segment
are bigger so that claim
rates have increased from 72% to 74% so
GDP which we say is 4977 crores there is a
650% increase in net on premium there
is an increase of about 12% 3726 crores and
profit after tax has been seen increasing by about 40%,
combine rates
are around 104 although the company is still saying
that it will be
around 102 by 25 so these are
the highlights of ICC Lombard now on the other
side there is also 18 coffee  The numbers came and here
we have seen that there is an
increase of almost 20% in profitability, about Rs 49
crore or the figure is 10% bigger in revenue, there has been a
slight improvement in the 8:00
clock coffee and instant coffee segment, that is why the
revenue got some support,
but now there is pressure on profit, about 4%
profit was seen sliding,
this figure of Rs 105 crore came, the
volumes here are a little lower and
input cost was seen, so you have to keep this
in mind also, the margins are around 14 and a half
percent, revenue in plantation business is
growing at 8%, but
some pressure is visible on profitability
and there is an
increase of 11% in revenue in value added products and a decline of 5% in profits,
these are the numbers of Tata Coffee
and prices of instant coffee are again
hyperspontaneous,
so from there also you have to monitor the stock, you were
also reading the line, in fact, the government has imposed a ban
on diesel exports
All taxes have been reduced to zero, just like on petrol,
but the government is imposing a tax of ₹6400 on domestic crude and production. If
we
talk about some of the former companies, Zydis
Liver has actually received approval from the USAF
for Astrol Transformer System, which is primarily
a drug to prevent post-mortem osteoporosis.
Now, its market size is around
$1.9 million and this
company will manufacture the drug in its Muria unit in Ahmedabad. On the other hand,
Tirumal Pharma has completed the USAF DIN inspection
in its sales bill manufacturing facility, so they will also
keep that stock with you.
Prestige has not directly reduced the amount by
about ₹66 crore. They have delisted this
park, they are wiring it and are taking 51%
stake in it. National Business
Development and
Construction Activity does office space,
commercial office space, so that
stock is also in Fox today.
Today's Events Calendar:
Penultimate Session in its place at 10:30 am.
Cabinet Meets  Schedule I am Sir Laxman uspe lage honge kuch
bhi